<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Cameron King</title><link>https://cameronking.me/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Cameron King</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 18:33:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cameronking.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Risus One-Pager</title><link>https://cameronking.me/risus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:23:12 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://cameronking.me/risus/</guid><description>Full RISUS rules can be found for free at DriveThroughRPG. It&amp;rsquo;s four whole pages, so take your time, and don&amp;rsquo;t hurt yourself trying to get through it all in one sitting.
Character Creation Grolfnar Vainsson the Viking Description: Tall, blond, and grinning. Likes to drink and fight and drink and chase Viking women and fight and sail the high seas and raid. Wants to write great sagas about himself. Clichés: Viking (4), Gambler (3), Womanizer (2), Poet (1) Describe your character with just enough detail that a picture forms in your mind.</description></item><item><title>Cypher System House Rules</title><link>https://cameronking.me/cypher/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:21:01 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://cameronking.me/cypher/</guid><description>I particularly like the Cypher System by Monte Cook Games. However, there are a few things that I houserule to make the game more appealing to my players (most of which are either younger, or do not regularly play Cypher games).
The most common combination of rules I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing with lately are one-shots using Roll d6 + Paperless + No Experience Points.
In a Nutshell MCG&amp;rsquo;s Cypher System is based on difficulties.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://cameronking.me/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 18:33:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cameronking.me/contact/</guid><description>Filling out this form will send me an email and an instant message. It is the best way to reach me if we are not already connected. If you prefer to communicate over Signal, Telegram, or WhatsApp, be sure to include that information below.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://cameronking.me/privacy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cameronking.me/privacy/</guid><description>Last updated: November 25, 2020
Introduction This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by This Website and how we use it.
Consent By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.
Log Files This Website follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics.</description></item><item><title>Terms and Conditions of Service</title><link>https://cameronking.me/tacos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cameronking.me/tacos/</guid><description>Last updated: November 25, 2020
Introduction These Terms of Service (&amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Terms of Service&amp;rdquo;) govern your use of our website located at https://cameronking.me (together or individually &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;) operated by This Website (&amp;ldquo;Company&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;).
Our Privacy Policy also governs your use of our Service and explains how we collect, safeguard and disclose information that results from your use of our web pages.
Your agreement with us includes these Terms and our Privacy Policy (&amp;ldquo;Agreements&amp;rdquo;).</description></item></channel></rss>